const level14Questions = [
 {
        question: "Ký ức, trí nhớ",
        answers: ["记忆 (jìyì)", "技艺 (jìyì)"],
        correct: "记忆 (jìyì)",
    },
        {
        question: "Ý tưởng, ý kiến",
        answers: ["注意 (zhùyì)", "主意 (zhǔyi)"],
        correct: "主意 (zhǔyi)",
    },
        {
        question: "Lợi hại",
        answers: ["厉害 (lìhai)", "利害 (lìhài)"],
        correct: "厉害 (lìhai)",
    },
        {
        question: "Mục đích",
        answers: ["目的 (mùdì)", "墓地 (mùdì)"],
        correct: "目的 (mùdì)",
    },
        {
        question: "Đồ trang sức",
        answers: ["首饰 (shǒushì)", "手势 (shǒushì)"],
        correct: "首饰 (shǒushì)",
    },
        {
        question: "Cuộc họp",
        answers: ["会议 (huìyì)", "回忆 (huíyì)"],
        correct: "会议 (huìyì)",
    },
        {
        question: "Giám đốc",
        answers: ["经历 (jīnglì)", "经理 (jīnglǐ)"],
        correct: "经理 (jīnglǐ)",
    },
        {
        question: "Luyện tập",
        answers: ["练习 (liànxí)", "联系 (liánxì)"],
        correct: "练习 (liànxí)",
    },
        {
        question: "Hoài bão, ước mơ",
        answers: ["抱负 (bàofù)", "报复 (bàofù)"],
        correct: "抱负 (bàofù)",
    },
            {
        question: "Bệnh viện",
        answers: ["医院 (yīyuàn)", "一院 (yīyuàn)"],
        correct: "医院 (yīyuàn)",
    },
            {
        question: "Mặt trời",
        answers: ["太阳 (tàiyáng)", "太痒 (tàiyǎng)"],
        correct: "太阳 (tàiyáng)",
    },
            {
        question: "Ban ngày",
        answers: ["白天 (báitiān)", "明白 (míng bái)"],
        correct: "白天 (báitiān)",
    },
            {
        question: "Nhà vệ sinh",
        answers: ["洗手间 (xǐshǒujiān)", "洗手 (xǐ shǒu)"],
        correct: "洗手间 (xǐshǒujiān)",
    },
            {
        question: "Áo khoác",
        answers: ["外套 (wàitào)", "衣服 (yīfu)"],
        correct: "外套 (wàitào)",
    },
            {
        question: "Cái đinh",
        answers: ["钉子 (dīngzi)", "锤子 (chuízi)"],
        correct: "钉子 (dīngzi)",
    },
];

export default level14Questions;